ShinY
深影
本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址http://shinybbs.vip
■
ShinY
深影
■
ShinY
深影
速度挺快 像子弹飞驰
Got one speed, that one. Bullet fast.
被围捕后 那头牛就不断飙窜
Damn cow been a dart since we rounded her up.
我不是说牛
Ain't talking about the cow.
她要学会套牛 我们兴许会失业
If she ever learns to rope, we might be out of a job.
说什么也不能教她
Whatever you do, don't teach her.
欲知一方水土是否未被探索
The best way to know if land is truly undiscovered
最好尝试用言语形容它
is to seek words to describe it.
若你无以言表 你便知它是处女地
When you can't, you know it's virgin land.
不曾被人类黑手所染指
Untouched by our dirty hands.
极目四望 唯余静默
To see it is to be silenced by it.
无垠土地令人叹为观止
Made speechless by its endless uniformity...
登丘望远 又见一马平川
To crest a rise is to see another that is identical.
人必须如航海家般望日牵星
One must read the sun and stars like a sailor
寻觅路途
to navigate this place.
一周已过 目之所及 鞠为茂草
We've seen nothing but grass for over a week:
没有飞禽走兽
no game, no birds, no snakes,
也无毒蛇蜥蜴
not even a lizard,
更渺无人迹
and no evidence the human race still exists.
可平原上尸骸遍野
But the plains are littered with bones.
人类黑手可在市井遁迹潜形
The dirty hand of man can go unnoticed in the city.
因为市井出自人类黑手
Because his dirty hand made the city.
殊不知在此地
But in this place,
纯真仿若矿物 渗透寸寸大地
where innocence is a mineral in the soil,
人类胆敢玷污 只怕祸患临头
the filth of our touch is an apocalypse.
他们来了
I see 'em.
该怎么办
What do we do?
管好牛群 不用担心他们
Keep holding the herd. Don't worry about them.
他们去缴税就行
They're just payin' the tax.
缴税
What tax?
在科曼切人领地放牧是要缴税的
You gotta pay a tax when you graze cattle in Comanche land.
但也并非必要
Well, you don't "Gotta",
如果你想避免枪战
but if you want to stay out of a gunfight,
那就必要...
it's a pretty good idea...
科曼切人有权收税吗
The Comanches can charge a tax?
这是他们的地盘
It's their land.
他们可以为所欲为
They can do whatever they want.
只有住在华盛顿的人
The only people who think this is America
还以为这里归美国管
still live in Washington.
那片洼地里有水源
There's water in this draw.
把牛群赶去那边
Push the herd to it.
我们在此处扎营
We'll make camp here.
先帮厨子整顿好
Carve one out for the cook first.
- 好的 - 遵命 警官
- All right. - Yes, sir.
不错
Yep.
走
Come on.
翻译 Fecit
翻译 邓前前
翻译 Monica爱吃蛋挞
翻译 小聪明
翻译 Noel
特效 Noel
压制 Toby
校对 Noel
《1883》 第七集 金发闪电
我的别烤太熟
For me, less fire.
知道 我给你们科曼切人做过饭
Yeah, I've cooked for you Comanche before.
我了解你们的口味
I know how you like it.
卧槽 你这是做什么
What the fuck do you think you're doin'?
你以为自己在干嘛
Huh? What the fuck do you think you're doing!
会说英语吗
Do you speak English?
你们这帮蠢货有谁会说英语
Who speaks English for this fucking circus?
我会
I do.
我只说一遍
I'm only going to tell you this once!
听着 都给我排队
All right, y'all get in line,
到桌子旁站成一列
you stand in a line besides the table!
拿好盘子和叉子
You grab a plate, you grab a fork,
等我给你们盛菜
then I give you the food!
吃完继续拿着盘子和叉子
When you're done you keep the plate, you keep the fork!
到河边洗干净 千万别弄丢
Go clean 'em in the creek but don't lose 'em!
不然你们得赔我三美元
Lose 'em you owe me three dollars
然后就用手吃饭吧
then you're eating with yer fucking hands.
"卧槽"是什么意思
What is this "Fuck?"
你是问我"卧槽"吗
Fuck did you just call me?
对 那什么是意思
Yes, what is this fuck?
他不懂这个词
He don't know what that word means.
他也不懂
Neither does he.
但他会去问她
But he's about to ask her.
那你便自求多福吧
Then Lord help you.
所以能别用这词了吗
So, maybe just don't use it. Hmm?
- 这毛病一时难改 - 那就开始改
- It's a hard one to shake. - Well, start shaking.
现在
Now!
妈妈 "卧槽"是什么意思
What does "Fuck" Mean, mama?
是指打屁股 你要是再说这词
It means a spanking, and a good one,
我会狠狠打你屁股
if you say it again.
他会被打屁股吗
Is he getting a spanking?
估计他等着挨训吧 儿子
Some form of one is probably headed his way, son.
没错 走吧
Mm-hmm. Come on.
排队
Line up!
他们怎么不排队
He says get in line and they don't.
他们是客人 客人不用排队
They're guests. Guests don't wait in line.
这些够吗
Isn't that good?
给他半份牛排吗
Half a steak for him?
好吧 整份牛排
Okay, a whole steak.
你再敢在我儿子面前说那词
You use that word in front of my child again...
我就拿叉子捅死你
I'm gonna stab you with this fucking fork.
- 遵命 女士 - 半份牛排就行
- Yes, ma'am. - Half a steak is fine.
快说谢谢
Say Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 谢谢 - 不客气 女士
- Thank you. - Yes, ma'am.
你知道吗 她算手下留情了
Just so you know, that could've gone a lot worse.
懂了
Lesson learned.
以后小心点
Yeah, we'll see about that.
看来她对那些臭印第安人有好感
I think she fancies those damn Indians.
女人心海底针啊
I wouldn't waste too much time worrying
别自寻烦恼了 伙计
about how that watch works, amigo.
你不会懂的
You ain't gonna figure it.
你的马挺不错
I like your horse.
它叫闪电
Lightning. That's his name.
为什么叫闪电
Why Lightning?
它跑得很快
Cause that's how fast he is.
眼见为实
Show me, then.
她要去哪里
Where is she going?
他们要比赛
They're gonna race.
干什么
They're going to what?
该死
Shit.
我觉得他们都疯了
I think the voice of reason has been muted.
亲爱的 看她那神情
Look at her face, honey.
看到了
I see it.
只希望她别垂头丧气
I just don't want to see it fall off.
看到她策马扬鞭的时候
The one place you ain't got to worry about her
你大可放心
is on the back of a horse.
开始吗
Y'all ready?
开始
Go!
她好像放下缰绳了
I think she dropped her reins.
对 确实放了
No. She let them go.
看到了吧
Lightning.
你还不信
Told ya.
我觉得你才是闪电
I think you are the lightning.
金色长发 快如闪电
Lightning with the yellow hair.
我应该这么称呼你
That's what I will call you.
金发闪电
Lightning Yellow Hair.
你怎么称呼
What do I call you?
萨姆
Sam.
Sam?
对
Sam.
为什么叫萨姆
Why Sam?
杀我妻子的人就叫萨姆
That was the name of the man who killed my wife.
我逼他说出名字
I know because I made him tell me.
然后杀了他 改了名
Then I killed him and took it.
我也杀了个人
I killed a man.
但我没想到用他的名字
But I didn't know to take his name.
你没有用最好
You don't want his name.
改成他的名字 你就永远活在悲伤中
With his name you mourn forever.
你叫闪电
Your name is Lightning.
闪电不会忧伤
Lightning doesn't mourn.
自然不会令你伤心
Doesn't do that either.
上天赐了你娇容
God gave you a good face.
还有金发
And yellow hair.
你需要把好刀
You need a better knife.
太贵重了
That's too much.
你刚赢了比赛
You won the race.
这把刀不属于我了
It's not mine anymore.
归你
It's yours.
还没睡
You're still up?
在多云天 我睡不着
I can't sleep when it's cloudy.
看着云彩 我不禁思考
Staring at clouds makes me think.
伴着星空 我才能入梦
I need stars to dream
又回到十八岁了
Oh, to be eighteen again...
- 你去哪里 - 梦游去厕所
- Where are you going? - To dream of indoor plumbing.
你开心吗
Are you happy?
是说这大半辈子 还是现在
In general or at this moment?
都有
Both.
这些年来
In general
我很担心
I'm worried.
当个贤妻良母
As a wife. As a mother.
我们的生活似乎
Our survival feels...
难以掌控
Beyond our control out here.
所以
So, no.
总之 我不开心
I'm not happy generally.
但此时此刻 有我爱的人
But in this moment, with the man I love,
可爱的儿子 令我羡慕的女儿...
a son I adore, and a daughter I envy...
我很开心
I am very happy.
要是你还不睡觉
However, if you don't get some sleep,
明天我可不会羡慕你了
I will not envy you tomorrow.
爱你
I love you.
大家以为雨来自云
People think because it's where rain comes from,
云满载水
clouds are filled with water.
怎会如此
But how can that be?
水怎么浮于天上又降落下来
How can water float above us then fall,
貌似重力听命于天空
as though gravity only applies to the sky
天空自有安排
when the sky lets it.
这也说明天空也会思考
But that would mean the sky thinks
云有生命 决定雨何时落
and clouds are alive and they decide to let it rain.
云又如何决定何处下雨
But how do they decide where to rain?
何时下雨...
And when...
为何云会让两地旱涝有别
Why do clouds choose to flood one place and deny another
直至大地龟裂 颗粒无收
until the earth cracks and field becomes desert?
或许重力本不存在
Maybe there's no such thing as gravity.
或许科学家们的发现均为谎言
Maybe everything scientists have "Discovered" Is a lie,
风正嘲讽我等
and wind is the world laughing at us.
最近强盗多吗
How's it been with bandits?
路上会越来越多
Worse the way you're going.
你们这帮人能强盗海捞一把
And you're the perfect size: big enough to be a prize,
不费吹灰之力
small enough to fight.
这里大多是些小偷
Here is mostly thieves.
北堪萨斯州和怀俄明州
North of Kansas and the Wyoming,
还在开战
they're still having a war.
马车队都不走那边
Wagons don't go that way anymore.
大家都坐火车
People take the train
要是有别的路 我早告诉你了
If I knew a way around I'd tell you.
他们也可以选择留在科罗拉多州
The way around is they decide to live in Colorado.
天公发怒
The sky is angry.
这里的小偷会利用风暴躲避
Thieves out here use the storms to hide.
记住了
I'll keep that in mind.
你们可以留下过夜 明早再走
You're welcome to stay the night, ride out in the morning.
明天风暴就来了
The storm will be here tomorrow.
你也走吧
You should leave, too.
能走倒好
I wish I could.
带他们去科罗拉多州吧
Take them to Colorado.
留他们在那里
Leave them there.
那样对他们更好
Better for them.
是啊
Yeah.
厨子走了
Cookie's gone.
去哪里了
Where'd he go?
不知道
Don't know.
没见着人
Just gone.
他不该从这里单独离开的
He wouldn't quit us. Not out here.
这相当于自杀
That's suicide.
他可能是想赶在风暴来前走
Maybe he trying to get ahead of the storm.
我们也该早点走
I wish we had.
我们不能再惯着他们了
I don't think we can baby 'em anymore.
要么硬着头皮走 要么等死
They're gonna have to get tough or die.
你怎么睡这里
Why are you sleeping here?
我想跟他一起睡在外面
I slept out there with him.
好吧
Fair enough.
我们得走了 你去赶牛群
We gotta get moving. Get to the herd.
风暴要来了
There's a storm coming.
走吧 亲爱的
Let's go, sweetie.
艾莎
Elsa...
艾莎 艾莎 别追它们
Elsa... Elsa, don't chase 'em!
这会让牛群分散的
You'll scatter the herd.
它们会去找个低地歇息
They'll head for low country and bed down.
风暴过后 我们再去找它们
We'll find them after it passes.
- 就放它们走吗 - 没错
- Just let them go? - Let them go.
停下马车 停下马车
Stop the wagon! Stop the wagon!
快下车
Get down now!
顺着风跑
Run into the wind,
找个低洼处趴下
find the lowest spot and lay down!
为什么要顺着风跑
Why into the wind?
免得东西砸你身上
So all this shit doesn't blow in on you.
快去
Go on!
把套具解开
Got to unhitch the horses!
- 什么 - 把套具解开
- What? - Got to unhitch the horses
不然马会拖着你跑的
before they run away with you!
我们给你备匹马
We'll saddle one for you
剩下的之后再管
and we'll pick the rest up later.
詹姆士
James...
那是什么
What is that?
龙卷风
Tornado.
别管马车了 快跑
Get rid of your wagon. Move.
还是来了
Here she comes.
抱着他
Take him.
趴下 儿子 趴下
Down. Down, son. Down.
卸下马鞍
Gotta pull the saddle.
艾莎怎么办
What about Elsa?
我们只能趴这么低了
This is as low as we're going to be able to get.
你帮不上我们什么忙
There's nothing you can do for us.
你打算怎么办
What are you gonna do?
你打算怎么办 詹姆士
What are you gonna do, James?
你要跟我们对抗龙卷风吗
You gonna fight this tornado when it comes for us?
我不知道 但我会待在这里
I don't know what I'm gonna do but I'm gonna do it right here.
她能活下来的
She's a survivor.
趴下
Lay down!
我们怎么办
What do we do?
跑
We run.
朝哪边
Which direction?
那边
That way.
没事的
Easy, boy.
让马走
Turn the horse loose.
它们不会有事吗
How will they make it?
没办法 让马走
They won't. Turn him loose.
我爱你
I love you.
走
Go!
- 我去找她 - 好
- I'm gonna go find her. - Okay.
我们去哪里 妈妈
Where are we going to go, mama?
我们去帮忙
We're gonna go help.
来吧 我们走
Come on, let's go.
要捡起来吗
Should we pick it up?
先找马
We look for horses first.
看来你俩都是闪电
I guess you're both Lightning.
风暴追不上你 对不对
Storm couldn't catch up to you, could it?
我去找其他马
I'll look for more.
你怎么带它们回来
How you gonna bring 'em back?
第一周真有意思
This has been a fun first week.
这活不算无聊
This deal ain't dull.
不仅遇上龙卷风
Got chased by a tornado
姑娘还被一印第安人抢走了
and lost a girl to an Injun at the same time.
从未拥有 何来失去
Gotta have it to lose it, partner.
我承认
I admit, uh...
可能我高估了自己的魅力
I might have overestimated my appeal.
你现在和昨天所见之处
Everything you see and everything
都是我的家
you saw yesterday is my home.
这里永远欢迎你 金发闪电
You're always welcome in it, Lighting with the Yellow Hair.
现在也是你的家了
It's your home too, now.
我就知道你没事
I knew you'd make it.
风暴追了我们一英里多
It chased us for a mile or more.
我们找地方趴下后
We found a spot to lay down
它就从我们身上掠过
and it went right over us.
现在你可以告诉别人
Well, now you can tell anybody who'll listen
自己从地狱活着回来了
that you lived through hell.
那不是地狱 爸爸
It wasn't hell, daddy.
它很美好
It was beautiful.
宝贝 那你经历的龙卷风
Well, baby girl, you must've been chased
肯定跟我的不同
by a different tornado than I was,
我只觉得是地狱
because my tornado was hell.
其他人没事吗
Rest of them make it?
他们在我后面
They're behind me.
去把他们带回来吧
Let's get 'em mounted up.
现在我们一无所有
Now we have nothing.
这让我们还怎么活
How do we survive with nothing?
但我们还有不可代替的东西
We didn't lose nothing you can't replace.
拿什么代替
Replace with what?
我们什么都没有
We have nothing.
没钱 没物
No money, nothing.
别急 我的钱够咱俩花
Look. I got money enough for the both of us...
你没损失什么
You ain't lose nothing.
现在我们...
Now let's...
看看能找到什么吧
Let's pick up what we can find.
约瑟夫
Josef?
Josef...
我要去找你的马了
I'll go look for your horse.
你觉得我们能找回多少辆马车
How many wagons you think we can salvage?
大概两辆
Maybe two.
算上剩下的这些有八辆
That makes eight with what's left.
载26个大人和22个小孩...
For twenty-six adults and twenty-two children...
不够
Ain't enough.
我知道
I know it.
最近的镇子在哪里 我们可以去买几辆
Where's the nearest town at where we can buy more?
丹佛 那得往回走
Denver. We gotta turn back.
如果半数人都走路肯定不行
They ain't gonna make it if half of them are walking.
坐马车去杜安渡口要一个月
It's a month to Doan's with wagons.
他们吃什么
What are they gonna eat?
能找到牛群就吃牛肉
Cattle if we can find 'em.
找不到就吃马肉
Horses if we can't.
- 我不会吃马肉的 - 我也不会
- I ain't eating no horse. - I ain't either.
那我们吃什么
So, what do we eat?
别吃了
I guess we don't.
你真带回来了
You made it.
谢谢
Thank you.
走吧 我们把牛赶到一起
All right, we'll gather up this herd.
以为你甩掉我们先走了
Thought maybe you quit us.
赶在风暴来前走而已
Just got ahead of the storm.
我也不是第一次穿越平原了
Ain't my first trip through the plains.
还以为你们都跟在后面
Figured y'all was right behind me.
我们本该跟着的
We should've been.
死了多少
How many died?
都活着
None.
看来让他们待着是正确的选择
Sounds like holding them back was the right choice, then.
晚上带队行进会折磨死人的
Running a team at night, that will pucker yer red eye.
我要把这马带回去
I'm gonna take this one back.
我跟你走
I'm right behind you.
见到那些牛没
Any chance you saw those cattle?
看到了 大概往后一英里吧
I saw 'em. About a mile back.
你队里的六个男人正把牛赶一块
Six of yer boys was gathering 'em up.
我们没有六个男的
We don't have six boys.
遇到贼了
We got thieves.
偷牛贼把牛赶到一起
Cattle thieves gathered the herd.
- 在哪里 - 往北几英里
- Where? - Couple miles north.
- 人数 - 六个
- How many? - Six.
赶紧去抓啊
Well, let's go get 'em.
我们可以先控制住牛群
We could hold the cattle up,
然后折返 跟在拓荒者后面
then double back and go after the pioneers next.
让他们把马车围成圈
Just have 'em circle the wagons.
没那么多马车
Ain't enough wagons to circle anymore.
你 我 还有托马斯去找牛
You, me, and Thomas go for the herd.
其余人守着马车队
The rest will stay with the wagons.
我要跟你一起
I'm going with you.
姑娘 你才参与过一场枪战
Young lady, you have been in your last gun fight.
你刚说他们折返或继续前进都有可能
You just said it's as likely they double back as move on.
又说后面有枪战 而你要去找牛
Then the gunfight's back there and you're here.
如果爆发枪战 我也陪着你
If there's gonna be a gunfight, I wanna be with you.
有人帮我说两句吗
Can I get some help here?
不好意思 貌似是她更有理
Sorry to say sounds like she's winning this argument.
找到他们后 你就原地不动
When we find 'em you sit still
等我们先解决他们 明白吗
till we're done with them, understand?
跟你们这帮人干活还真是不同寻常
This is the strangest outfit I ever worked for.
你得多动脑子
It'll test yer noggin.
你想告诉她吗
You wanna tell her?
当然不会 我不想告诉她
Hell, no, I don't wanna tell her.
总得跟她说点什么
We gotta tell her something.
那些拓荒者找到步枪没
Them pioneers find their rifles?
找到一些 都在那边
Found a few. They're right there.
我得拿去分给大家
I'd get them loaded and handed out.
为什么
Why?
似乎有贼顺走了我们的牛
Looks like some thieves picked up our cattle.
我不确定是真是假 但他们可能回来
I doubt it'll happen this way, but they could double back.
我丈夫呢
Where's my husband?
找牛去了
Went after them.
我女儿呢
Where's my daughter?
她说世上最安全的地方就是他身后
She said the safest place on earth is right behind him.
我希望你们待在这里
I want you boys to sit here
舍命保护好我儿子
and guard my son with your life.
把马给我
I need your horse.
为什么
Why?
我好去找她
So I can go get her.
赶紧给我下马
Get off the goddam horse.
你要用命保护我儿子
You guard my son with your life.
听明白了吗
You understand me?
好的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
我知道那姑娘随谁了
I see where the girl gets it.
有其母必有其女
Apple don't fall far.
你们想抓蚱蜢吗
Y'all wanna hunt for grasshoppers?
想
Sure.
这可不止六个人 警官
That ain't six, Captain.
我觉得有十二个
I count twelve.
是十三个
Thirteen.
撤 兵分多路
Run. And fan out wide.
你继续跑 千万别停
You keep running, don't stop, no matter what!
我毫无畏惧
I felt no fear.
只当作新的比赛罢了
It simply became another race.
我们惧怕未知
We fear what we don't know.
我知道结果如何
I knew what would happen.
要么赢 要么死
I would win the race or I would be killed.
结果如此简单 反倒让人舒心
There was comfort in the simplicity of it.
尽管蹄声逼近
Even though I could hear hooves getting closer,
我仍不畏惧
I felt no fear.
杀戮让人惊恐
There is horror to every killing.
不管正当与否
Even when it's justified.
亲手杀人时 我倍感惶恐
Even when I killed, I was horrified.
但看到萨姆杀人之时 宛如眼看
But watching Sam kill was like watching a lion
雄狮扑食
hurl itself into a deer.
他的怒火炽烈燃烧 无暇恐惧
His fury was so magnificent, there was no time for horror.
更无心手下之人
Not even for the men he killed.
我不禁自问
I questioned my mind.
最后倒下的或许是我
I wondered if I am the one who is dead
刚才的事可能是幻梦
and this is all a dream.
看着他扬鞭远去 我决定苏醒
I watched him ride away and decided I must be awake.
我不能死
I must be alive.
我要追寻他
Then I chased after him.
严重吗
How bad?
皮带都打穿了
Went through your belt.
快脱掉
Take it off.
我去 子弹还没进去
What the hell? It sits right there.
快取出来
Get it out.
应该能挤出来
I think I can squeeze it out.
给你儿子当纪念品
Little souvenir for your son.
一颗没射死你的子弹
The bullet that didn't kill you.
有处跳弹伤
Just a ricochet.
伤口不深
Ain't in too deep.
还是得把子弹弄出来
Still got to dig that lead out.
另一处呢
How's the other one?
只是擦伤
Just skinned me.
你这辈子的运气都用光了吧 托马斯
I think you used up the last of your luck, Thomas.
你的伤呢
How bad is your'n.
我没中枪
I didn't get hit.
该死 怎么搞的
Shit. What the hell?
我找不到
I can't find it.
你看到了吗
Do you see it?
转身
Turn around.
肯定哪里中弹了
Got to be coming from somewhere.
警官 帽子摘掉
Take off your hat, Captain.
我还差点没命
I'll be damned.
现在你的运气也耗尽了 警官
Now you used up all your luck, too, Captain.
我没错的话 这匹是你的吧 托马斯
If I recall, Thomas, this one is yours.
没错
She is.
谢伊 我敢说
I swear, Shea,
每次你好高骛远 想干大事
when you bite off more than you can chew,
肯定能成
you sure bite big.
我大言不惭地告诉你
I ain't ashamed to say it,
查理 你真是慧眼识珠
you are a beautiful sight, Charlie.
你这家伙怎么也在这里
What the hell are you doing out here?
跟你一样 来找强盗和离群的牛
Same as you apparently. Hunting bandits and strays.
不过 现在看来你把事情都搞定了
Though you seem to herd all your bandits up at once.
非常感谢
Hell, we sure appreciate you.
追杀偷牛贼可是西部的五大乐趣
Killing cattle thieves is one the West's five great pleasures.
不必言谢
No need for thanks.
要谢就谢他们吧
You can save your thanks for them.
我们不光会谢他们
We'll do more than that.
你只有五种乐趣了吗
You're only up to five now?
我很挑剔的 警官
Well, I'm pickier than you, sir.
我还喜欢骏马 坐上马鞍看日出
I added horse and sunrise from the saddle
在原野策马扬鞭 这些能算一种乐趣
and riding the wild country, I thought they deserved a spot.
你早就有这打算了吧
I thought they was already on your list.
不 刚想起来的
No, just added.
我不想起太早
Don't like to get up that early.
你受伤了
You're hurt.
我没事
I'm fine.
你呢
Are you fine?
我也没事
I'm fine, too.
恐怕你没心思埋掉他们吧
Don't suppose you care to bury these folks?
查理 老实说
Tell you the truth, Charlie,
拿他们填沟壑不值当
I don't think they're worth the hole.
你的营地呢
Where's your camp?
我知道
I know it.
他们或许真该死
Well, they may not deserve it
但总得有人给这些混蛋
but someone should say a prayer
做个祷告
over these sorry sons of bitches.
你应该不想听
I doubt you care to hear.
没错
I don't.
我要回去跟大部队汇合
We need to get back to our people.
营地见
We'll meet you there.
■
更多精彩 请登录深影论坛 shinybbs.vip
深影字幕组微博 weibo.com/syfansub
■
关注深影字幕组
微信公众号，更
多影视资讯，等
你来发现
艾莎
Elsa?
Elsa!
把马交出来
Give me your horse.
我没在...
I ain't aski...
等我们回到营地 她会沉默不语
She wouldn't speak when we got back to camp.
不愿见我父亲 也不愿见我
Wouldn't look at my father... Wouldn't look at me.
我曾听她在篝火前啜泣
I heard her crying by the fire before dawn.
我坐过去问她怎么了
I sat beside her and asked her what was wrong.
她说她杀死了一个骑马的人
She said she killed a man over a horse.
我们全家只有约翰有机会上天堂
And now John was the only hope our family has to reach Heaven.
我不敢告诉她不必寻觅天堂
I didn't have the heart to tell her there is no Heaven to go to,
我们已身处其中
because we're in it already.
我们也身处地狱 两者并存
We're in hell, too. They coexist.
相依相成
Right beside each other.
而大地即上帝
And God is the land.